stighlorgan.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy - Stighlorgan

**Privacy Policy**

Privacy and online safety are important to Stighlorgan. This policy explains how we may collect information about you and then how we use it. It also gives certain assurances on things that we will and what we will not do.

**1\. Purpose and consent for collection**

Stighlorgan collects, stores, processes or transmits data in order to provide Services to Customers. This may include marketing of services, the processing of orders for Customers and customer support activities, or for the purposes of conducting corporate activities such as interacting with suppliers, job applicants or administration.  
By providing personal information to Stighlorgan in any of the ways described in this policy, the Subject is agreeing that they are authorised to provide the information and that they accept this privacy policy and that Stighlorgan is authorised to process it.

Stighlorgan will collect a range of information about the Subject, either via activity via our website, emails, customer support, telephone, in person or at trade shows. This information includes:  
Name  
Organisation  
Address  
Phone number  
Email address  
IP address  
Username  
Credit/debit card details  
We will not collect sensitive categories of data without their explicit consent.

Stighlorgan does not undertake any automated decision making relating to any Service activities except for third party fraud checking services that may automatically decline a credit or debit card transaction.  
Stighlorgan will not collect data relating to minors as defined under UK law. Minors as defined by UK law are not permitted to use Stighlorgan Services or interact with us as a corporate entity.  
Stighlorgan may from time to time contact the Customer via email regarding service related matters such as billing, product support and logistics.

**2.  ** **Data retention  
**We will keep your personal information for as long as you are a customer of Stighlorgan.  
After you stop being a customer, we may keep your data for longer so we able to respond to any questions or complaints and to comply with any legal and accounting requirements.

**3.Data transfers and the use of Data Sub Processors  
**Stighlorgan will not share Subject data with a third party not directly associated with the provision of services without their explicit consent. Stighlorgan will also not transfer Subject data to a third party country outside of the UK or EEA that is not compliant with the applicable data protection laws via adequacy agreement, Binding Corporate Rules or other legally appropriate means as defined by the Information Commissioner’s Office without their explicit consent.  
At Stighlorgan we make use of a number of 3rd party organisations so that we can deliver services to our customers. Whilst the following list is not intended to be exhaustive, Stighlorgan typically only transfers the personal data relating to our customers, where required for the activities set out below, to the following third parties or Data Processors:

**Supplier** |  **Why?** |  **Privacy Policy** |  **Basis for processing**  
---|---|---|---  
SiteGround Hosting Ltd |  Website hosting |  [View](https://www.siteground.co.uk/privacy.htm) |  Legitimate Interests  
MailChimp |  Email marketing |  [View](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy) |  Consent  
Stripe Inc. |  Payment Processing and fraud prevention |  [View](https://stripe.com/gb/privacy) |  Contractual  
Paypal Inc. |  Payment Processing and fraud prevention |  [View](https://www.paypal.com/uk/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full) |  Contractual  
Google |  Analytics, Geolocation, Marketing |  [View](https://policies.google.com/privacy) |  Legitimate Interests  
Facebook |  Marketing  |  [View](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update) |  Legitimate Interests  
ManageWP |  Backups and security monitoring |  [View](https://managewp.com/privacy) |  Legitimate Interests  
Google |  Analytics, Geolocation, Marketing |  [View](https://policies.google.com/privacy) |  Legitimate Interests  
Facebook |  Marketing  |  [View](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update) |  Legitimate Interests  
Cloudflare Inc. |  Website Security and performance optimisation. |  [View](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/) |  Legitimate Interests  
  
By interacting with Stighlorgan as defined in this policy, the Subject provides their consent for this transfer and use of our Data Processors and their Data Sub-Processors, and for transfer to any other appropriate third party Data Processor for the purposes of delivery of the Services and customer relationship management activities.

**4.Commitment to confidentiality and security of processing  
**Stighlorgan uses appropriate technical and organisational security measures within our sphere of responsibility to ensure an appropriate level of confidentiality and integrity.  
Should there be a concern regarding a possible security incident or data breach, please email [info@stighlorgan.com](mailto:info@stighlorgan.com)

**5.Cookies  
**Cookies are small text files that are stored in a computer’s web browser memory. They help website providers with things like understanding how people use a website, remembering a User’s login details, and storing website preferences. We use cookies and other similar technologies to help us ensure that our Services function properly, prevents fraud and other harm, and analyze and improve the Services in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**5 a) How We Use Cookies.**

We change the cookies periodically as we improve or add to our Services, but we generally use cookies for the following purposes:

  1. **To Operate Our Services**. Some cookies are essential to the operation of our website and Services. We use those cookies in a number of different ways, including:

  * **Authentication**. We use cookies to remember your login state so You don’t have to login again as you navigate through our site. 
  * **Fraud Prevention and Detection.** Cookies and similar technologies that we deploy on or website help us monitor for and detect potentially harmful or illegal use of our Services.
  * **Site Features and Services**. We use cookies to remember what products you have in your basket during your shopping experience.

  1. **To Analyze and Improve Our Services.** Cookies help us understand how to make our website and customer services work better for You. Cookies tell us how people reach our website and they give us insights into improvements or enhancements we need to make to our website and Services.
  2. **For Better Advertising**. Cookies can help us provide more effective advertising on our website. For example, we might use a cookie to help prevent You from seeing the same advertisement multiple times or to measure how many times an advertisement is viewed or clicked on.

**5 b) How We Use Other Technologies**

  1. **Pixel tags**. Pixel tags (also known as web beacons and clear GIFs) may be used in connection with some Services to, among other things, track the actions of Users (such as email recipients), measure the success of our marketing campaigns and compile statistics about usage of the Services and response rates.
  2. **Third Party Analytics**. We use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and similar technologies, to collect and analyze information about use of the Services and report on activities and trends. This service may also collect information regarding the use of other websites, apps and online resources. To help protect Your privacy we anonymize personally identifiable information like IP addresses.

**5 c) How To Manage Cookies**

Your web browser may allow You to change Your cookie preferences. Please consult the help section of Your web browser or follow the links below to understand Your options, but please note that if You choose to disable the cookies, some features of our website or Services may not operate as intended.  
Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en  
Explorer: https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/products/windows?os=windows-10  
Safari: https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411  
Firefox: https://support.mozilla.org/products/firefox/cookies  
Opera: http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/

**5 d) Cookie Table**

Cookies that we commonly use are listed below. This list is not exhaustive, but describes the main reasons we typically set cookies.

_ga  
_gid  
_gat |  These cookies are used by Google Analytics to distinguish different users and provide analytics.  
---|---  
aelia_cs_selected_currency |  These cookies remember what currency you have set in for our store.  
woocommerce_cart_hash  
woocommerce_items_in_cart  
woocommerce_items_in_cart |  These cookies store your shopping cart information – so we can remember what’s in your basket between pages / visits.  
slg_count |  This cookie makes sure you only see our mailing list promotion once, so it’s not annoying.  
  
**6\. Advertising**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements regarding goods and services that may be of interest to You when You access our websites, based on Data relating to Your access to and use of our websites on any of Your devices. To do so, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie, or similar tracking technology, on Your browser (including the use of pixel tags). They may also use these technologies, along with data they collect about Your online use, to recognize You across the devices You use, such as a mobile phone and a laptop, and to make decisions about the advertisements You see. If You would like more information about this practice, and to learn how to opt out of behavioural advertising delivered by Network Advertising Initiative member companies in desktop and mobile browsers on the particular device on which You are accessing this Privacy Policy, please visit the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/).

You may download the [AppChoices app](http://youradchoices.com/appchoices) to opt out in mobile apps. In order to understand and improve the effectiveness of our advertising, we may also use web beacons, cookies, and other technologies to identify the fact that You have visited our website or seen one of our advertisements, and we may provide that Data to one or more third-party advertising networks. 

The Data we provide may include the time and date of Your visit to our website, pages viewed, links clicked and other information that does not disclose Your ‘real world’ identity. Those advertising networks may recognize the web beacon or cookie associated with Your visit to our website when You visit other websites on which they serve advertising, and they may make decisions about the advertisements You see based on it. 

**7\. Email Marketing**

If you are subscribed to our mailing list and no longer wish to receive emails from us please unsubscribe below:  

**8\. Get in touch**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time, or discuss any other data protection matters with us, by contacting us at [info@stighlorgan.com](mailto:info@stighlorgan.com) ** ** or write to Stighlorgan, 1 Stoke Newington Road, Dalston, London N16 8BH

Data Subjects, Controllers or any other concerned parties wishing to discuss matters relating to data protection, such as a Subject Access Request or concern over accuracy of collected data, please email [info@stighlorgan.com](mailto:info@stighlorgan.com) ** ** or write to Stighlorgan, 1 Stoke Newington Road, Dalston, London N16 8BH. The email address is monitored within working hours and you should receive a reply within 3 working days.
